thecassiopeia.com 2001-10-23

# Privacy Policy For Internet Business Consultants For 3rd Millennium

with respect to information gathered on their web pages. Such information is received by the above and the Partners. 

  The terms "we" and "us" refer to the above.

  **The Information We Collect**

  This notice applies to all information collected on the above websites, or submitted to the above and Partners at any time through any Service Pages. Personally Identifiable Information— may include your name and contact information, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, shipping and billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, behavior patterns, purchase history and other information. We collect **prospect information** , which may include name and contact information of individual(s) you think would be interested in our services. For **Partners** , the information we collect may include your name and contact information, your site's category, your website information (URL, visitors per day, page views per month, services offered), payment information (check payee, SSN/Tax ID, bank information), and user-comments.

  Aggregate Information—We collect non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and services, and share the aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties.

  Each of the Partners has access to information specific to their site only. Each Partner will determine what it will do with the collected information; however, each Partner has individually agreed to abide by this Privacy Policy, Partner Agreement, and End-User Agreement.

  **Collection of Personal Information from Children under Thirteen**

  We do not allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to register for any services.

  **The Way We Use Information**

  We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which the information is intended. Such transactions may include administering a service, such as email, search, community, advertising sales, ecommerce, completing an order, shipping a product, replying to support requests or contacting you if you have granted us permission to do so. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Partners and End-Users.

  From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of additions or improvements in our services. When supplying name and contact information, you can indicate your preference to receive or not receive information and updates about Partner's services or special offers from other companies, programmes or other registration processes.

  We may also use personally identifiable End-User information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to End-Users based on their demographic and behavioural information.

  Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways or for reasons unrelated to the ones described above without also providing an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

  **Online Support Forum**

  When using the online "Support" forum of our website to post your questions and/or comments, you will be asked to indicate your name, email address, and message. When posting your message, your name, email address, and message are publicly displayed and available to anyone who may visit those pages on which you have posted your questions and/or comments.

  **Our Commitment to Data Security**

  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, in co-operation with our Partners, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

  In addition, personnel who have access to our database are trained to maintain and secure all information.

  **How You Can Access or Update Your Information**

  **Partners** , you can access all your personally identifiable information that we and the Partners collect online and maintain by logging into your password-protected (SSL encrypted) account and selecting to update your "Profile."  
**End-Users** , you can access your information by logging into your password-protected End-User account and selecting to update your "Personal Info." You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly documents and explains error.

  If you have submitted information on our site but do not currently have an account with us, you can access and correct the information that we collect and maintain by contacting us.

  To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

  **How to Contact Us**

  Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us at the  Contact Us or email us ([ webmaster@thecassiopeia.com](mailto:webmaster@thecassiopeia.com)) 

**Email, Search, and Community Specific Terms and Conditions**

 To provide you with these services, we partner with Everyone.net. Everyone.net and we consider email transmitted via our service to be private correspondence between the sender and recipient. Therefore, none of us will monitor, edit, or disclose the contents of your private communications, except for reasons provided for in the [End-User Agreement](http://www.everyone.net/main/html/agreement_enduser.html).

  Content posted to public community areas is publicly available and Everyone.net reserves the right to remove any publicly posted content that is objectionable.

  **Advertising Sales Specific Terms and Conditions**

  We work with third parties that serve ads to our network of sites. These third parties may use the demographic and/or behavioural data provided by Partners to deliver relevant, targeted advertisements to the Partner Site. This demographic and behavioural data is obtained and maintained in a manner such that no connection can be drawn between the profiles supplied to the third parties and the End-User's personally identifiable information.

  To find out more about how Engage Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on one of our Network, please go to [ http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html).  
To find out more about how DoubleClick manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on our Network, please see the commitment to protect internet user privacy at [ http://www.doubleclick.net:8080/privacy_policy](http://www.doubleclick.net:8080/privacy_policy).  
To find out more about how Advertising.com manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on our Network, please go to <http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html>.

  **Conclusion**

In case you have any more questions on the topic, please email us at the above addresses.

**Internet Business Consultants For 3rd Millennium** **Home** About Us Privacy Policy Contact Us  Link To Us **Copyright 2000-2001 ©© theCassiopeia.com All Rights Reserved**
